Guide to the Poly Archives Historic Photograph Collection RG.026
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series VII: Events, 9953
  - Subseries G: Lynford Lecture Series, 12787
    - Lynford Lecture Series- Dr. Robert Mendell 2002, 2002 October 8; cuid859; 12791 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Lynford Lecture Series- Gerald M. Rubin 2003, 2003 October 20; cuid860; 12794 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Lynford Lecture Series- Dr. Richard L. Garwin 2004, 2004 November 4; cuid861; 12795 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Subseries H: Miscellaneous Events, 12812
    - Art Show Opening, 1998 November 19; cuid862; 12817 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Baby Photo Contest, 2001 January; cuid863; 12820 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Big Apple College Fair, 1986; cuid864; 13393 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Caretech, 1999 February; cuid865; 12833 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - CATT Workshop, 1997 November 24; cuid866; 12842 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - CATT Review Conference, 1998 October; cuid867; 12843 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Chinese Delegation, 1998 June; cuid868; 12846 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Chinese New Year's, 1995 January 31; cuid869; 12847 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - City Hall Paint Study, undated; cuid870; 13311 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Co-Op Education, 1964; cuid871; 12851 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Colorado School Shooting Support, 1999; cuid872; 12853 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - David Chang & Michael G. Carey, 2001 February 9; cuid873; 12855 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - E-Commerce with Senator Schumer, 2000 August 28; cuid874; 12864 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Events, 1980s; cuid875; 12867 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Events 1992, cuid876; 13032 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Events 1993, cuid877; 12868 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Events 1994, cuid878; 12869 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Events, Miscellaneous, undated; cuid879; 12870 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Exec 21 Program, undated; cuid880; 12871 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Fall Dance, 1965-1966; cuid881; 12878 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Fire Test, 1970s; cuid882; 12883 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Foundation Grant, undated; cuid883; 12884 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Gassner Mural 2001, 2001 October 10; cuid884; 12885 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Goldsmith Opening, 1996 October 19; cuid885; 12887 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Guardian Chemical, 1960s; cuid886; 12890 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - High School Science Fair, 1997 March 26; cuid887; 12891 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Intel Science Talent Search, 1999 February; cuid888; 12901 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Israel Reunion, 1999 January 10; cuid889; 12902 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Israel Commencement, 2000; cuid890; 12903 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Israel Trip, undated; cuid891; 12904 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Jacobs Events, 1992-1994; cuid892; 12911 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Japanese TV Interview, 1992 August 11; cuid893; 13037 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Knowledge Workers Educational Alliance, 1999 October; cuid894; 13031 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Laptop Distribution, 2000 August, 30; 2000 September 13; cuid895; 12914 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Laptop Orientation, 2000 August 30; cuid896; 12915 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Logicon Technology Day, 2000, 2000 March; cuid897; 12919 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Logicon Technology Day, 2001, 2001 April 12; cuid898; 12920 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Managerial Techniques Workshop 1968, 1968 March-April; cuid899; 12922 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Mayor's Award for Excellence in Science and Technology, 2000 March 8; cuid900; 12925 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Memorial Plaque, 1973; cuid901; 12926 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Metro Cafe Awards, 2002 May 2; cuid902; 12928 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Events, undated; cuid903; 12931 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous Events, 1936-1956; cuid904; 12932 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Events, undated; cuid905; 12933 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous Events, undated; cuid906; 12934 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous Events, undated; cuid907; 12935 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Events, undated; cuid908; 12936 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Multicultural Crafts Festival, 1998 December 3; cuid909; 12945 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Natural History & Dinosaur Book Exhibit, 2000; cuid910; 12949 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - NYC First, 2001 March 16; cuid911; 12953 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - NYC Mathematics, Science, and Technology Fair, 1999 March 2; 2004 March 17; cuid912; 12954 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - NYC Science & Technology Fair, 2001 May 24; cuid913; 12956 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - NYC Science & Engineering Fair, 2002 March 13; cuid914; 12955 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Open House, 1997, 1997 October 26; cuid915; 12958 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Open House, 1998, 1998 October 25; cuid916; 12959 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Open House, 1999, 1999 October 24; cuid917; 12960 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Othmer Institute, 2001 September 4; cuid918; 12961 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Paint-a-thon, 1996 March 31; cuid919; 12965 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Poly Expo, 1992 June; cuid920; 13392 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Polytech Paints the Town, 1996; cuid921; 12974 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - R & R Summer Social, 2002 June 21; cuid922; 12976 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Raising the Bar on Hi-Tech Incubators 2000, 2000 March 29; cuid923; 12977 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Science Fair, 1996, cuid924; 12981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Science Fair, 1998, cuid925; 12982 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Science & Technology Forum, 1998, cuid926; 12984 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Science & Technology Forum, 2000, 2000 May 25; cuid927; 12985 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Sculpture Installation, 2002 October 8; cuid928; 13038 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Sculpture, 2002 October 8; cuid929; 13039 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - September 11th Poster, 2001; cuid930; 12990 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - September 11th Attack, 2001 September 14; cuid931; 12991 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Solutions at Silleck, 2001 February 28; cuid932; 12992 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Spotlight on Scholars, 1999 March 20; cuid933; 12993 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Summer Research Closing Ceremonies, 1998; cuid934; 12996 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Symbol Wireless Technology, 2000 July; cuid935; 12998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Symbol Wireless Technologies Barbeque 2001, 2001 April 25; cuid936; 12999 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Taiwan Visit, 1996 January 23; cuid937; 13000 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Teacher's Computer Seminar, 2000 June 28; cuid938; 13001 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Time Capsule, 1960; cuid939; 13120 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Tri-tech Agreement, 1984; cuid940; 13073 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - United Technologies- Norden Systems, Grant Presentation, 1984; cuid941; 13004 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Unity Day 2001, 2001 September 19; cuid942; 13005 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Unity Day 2002, 2002 September 11; cuid943; 13006 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - USI Opening Session, 2002 October 7; cuid944; 13007 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Vision 2000, undated; cuid945; 13008 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Welcome Back Reception, 1995 September 14; cuid946; 13011 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Westchester Expo, 1997; cuid947; 13015 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Series VIII: Miscellaneous, negatives, and contact sheets, 13123
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated; cuid948; 13168 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, Non-Poly, undated; cuid949; 13394 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Contact Sheets, undated; cuid950; 13163 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Contact Sheets, undated; cuid951; 13170 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Contact Sheets, undated; cuid952; 13171 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Contact Sheets, undated; cuid953; 13078 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, undated; cuid954; 13169 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, undated; cuid955; 13172 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, undated; cuid956; 13173 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, undated; cuid957; 13174 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, undated; cuid958; 13175 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Slides, undated; cuid959; 13395 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Photo Labels without Photos, undated; cuid960; 13125 (Box 22, Folder 37)